# Tim Phillips, Designer

#### **About**

My passion for design centres around the individual details, interactions and systems that work in unison to create cohesive user experiences.

I relish the opportunity to engage with projects at their inception, as well as to dive into established problem spaces.

#### Contact

Email timphillips1991@gmail.com Web timphillipsdesign.com.au Phone +61 409 888 443

#### Education

## Swinburne University of Technology

- Bachelor Design(Communication Design) (2012)
- Diploma of Graphic Design (2010 - 2011)

### Skills

Lo/Hi-fi mockups, Design thinking, Prototyping, Concept ideation, Usability testing, User research, Interaction design, Visual design, Wireframing

#### References

Available on request

# Résumé

# Experience

### <u>Carsales</u> (2021 - present)

I'm currently working as the product designer in the Digital Retailing team, designing their consumer facing product, SELECT, across web and native platforms. The SELECT project aims to enable consumers to complete more parts of the car buying journey online.

### <u>Assembler</u> (2020 - 2021)

I worked as the Lead Product Designer for Assembler. Leading the design across their range of platforms, as well as creating their design system. I also supported the engineering team with front-end web development.

### PwC Australia (2018 - 2020)

Working within PwC Australia's
New Ventures unit, I led the product
design and front-end web development
within the Automation Engine team.
This technology was used by internal
teams to build and manage web
applications.

# <u>The Just Group</u> (2017 - 2018)

Predominantly worked on the Smiggle brand, designing web and email content for their global market base (AU, UK, IRE and Asia at the time). Also working across the Just Group's other core brands in varying capacities.

View prior experience (2016 - 2011)